Working in the UK, you're expected to
use all of your holiday and that's not
seen as a bad thing. You're actively
encouraged to do it. Your bosses are on
you like, "Make sure you take your time
off." And I always thought that was very
supportive. It was never I was never
made to feel like it was bad that I was
taking time off. It was always just
making sure that it fitted with
everybody else's schedule.
>> Yeah, there's no sort of bonus points
for not having a rest. Although having
said that, I think often CEOs and stuff
will publicly praise people who work
longer hours and show that they're
sacrificing their personal time for the
company.
>> But I don't know if I've seen CEOs say
you should take less holiday.
>> There's a culture of like work hard,
play hard. You should have a decent, you
know, relaxing holiday because you've
worked so hard.
>> Yeah, that is a thing in quite a lot of
industries, work hard, play hard.
>> [music]